bring it back to the rapping is that you
said that people didn't want to hear you
rap you know and I I I I know a lot of
rappers I know a lot of people in the
community that never give up on their
dreams but they're not also listening to
the people what the people want and that
shows that you know a lot about business
a lot about marketing did you have any
like uh experience behind that like did
you go to school did you get a degree in
it like what what did you like where did
you get all of that Knowledge from
here's the thing I've been on the
internet since the internet was was born
right I was on infos seek searching when
infos seek was here when geoc cities was
here I use knowledge and I look man I am
I pay attention to a lot of things so no
I didn't go to school I went to the
School of Hard Knocks I went to the
school of experience I went to the
school of failure I went to the school
of try try again I read a tons of book
on the subject if I'm interested I'm
going to learn it my friend so no and
here's the thing with with rapping cuz I
could keep pushing that door down right
we could keep pushing that rapper door
down but I wasn't living on purpose so
there's a lot of purposeful rappers out
here that's living on purpose that's
their thing but my thing is to teach
Millions how to get uncomfortable to
think better act better and live better
so I wasn't on purpose so no matter how
much and we're live but I'm just getting
folks I'm just getting set up we're just
a little bit few minutes behind but
that's okay we're Hustlers we we take
advantage of the
situation you know we don't we break the
rules we don't follow the rules I don't
know can you guys see me right
now can you guys see me right
now just let me
know
oops one second
here let me see I'm going to I'm going
to log in right in right now now that
video
clip
okay can they see me can you see me can
you guys hear me oh yeah you guys you
guys can okay all right welcome to the
hustle
Zone yo this is my name is RP the god
AKA The Hustle Zone the king of the
hustle Zone AKA um the wizard you know
why because I make [ __ ] happen and today
and today to day I was able to score the
be the biggest moment of the hustle zone
for me you know as soon as I saw this
lady go and Grace the Facebook live
stage I fell in love because she brought
the heat she brought the heat right so
uh I'm going to let her in introduce cuz
you if you guys know her you know how
she's going to introduce herself and I'm
going I go ahead go ahead Stacy hey hey
hey hey hey
Comfort Killers I am Stacy AC cross and
there is no e in my name Ryan Perez that
b Stacy I had to I I had to shave I
shave for you today and I put on my bow
tie because I I feel like you know you
you're honoring the show by coming on
you know I I was so happy to see you
sister on um on Grand Cardone show you
know cuz Grant Cardone UNC Uncle G you
know like oh my God oh my goodness oh my
God what am I doing I wasn't supposed to
be there that's totally unreasonable and
unrealistic man it's illogical man so
I'm not supposed to be there Ryan yeah I
tell like you know I've seen so many
people talk about Gary ve and and and
and and uh uh they talk about Grant card
they talk about one day I'm going to get
there and as soon as I met you Stacy you
were on there and you were killing it
you killing it no no hold on can I say
something you w you you weren't on there
I'm sorry he was on your show thank you
sir he was on your show thank you sir
the Comfort killer show on GCV baby you
had it wrong but you corrected yourself
and I love it yes because you are a
hustle so I'm okay folks this is the
hustle Zone we captured the spirit of
the entrepreneur because you know what a
lot of times just people see the success
and people don't truly understand the
story on how these entrepreneurs get
here mean there's a lot of Blood Sweat
and Tears that go into the hustle and so
when when we have a guest on the show we
always ask them the first question in
Stacy and we have we have a half an hour
I want you to tell us your story like
tell us your story tell us how this all
all came to be right all right so I'm
going to go back it's gonna seem like
it's just in recent history but this
thing started for me a very long time
ago man I think we all have that
entrepreneurial spirit in our blood and
our bones deep into the crevices under
the flap of our freaking stomach flaps
so here's the deal man I was selling I
was selling pens and pencils for nickels
in middle school I was using other kids
toys in a garage sale and yard sale hey
I knocked doors to shovel people's snow
but it wasn't always good right I grew
up we we came from Jamaica I got
kidnapped in Jamaica man they brought my
ass back they brought me back to the
police station I'm too hot I'm on fire
they said but it wasn't always good cuz
my family came to America in the 80s man
I was born in Jamaica we came for the
American dream I couldn't find the
American dream I did what what everyone
wanted me to do right I went to school
we went to high school bad grades went
to college bad grades why the why the
[ __ ] can't I understand what's going on
right so I know I'm intelligent because
I got it in my blood and I got it in my
gut so let's let's let's fast forward to
when this thing really started see I was
a rapper I always used to play with
words I'm a word Smith word play I play
a lot of games with words so I left that
alone right I left that alone because
nobody wanted to hear me rap so I said
what do people want from me what is this
universe want from me what am I here for
what what am I here for God but instead
of looking up Ryan I looked within and I
found that my true calling was helping
was helping people get uncomfortable to
think better to act better and to live
better Ryan so I went to a seminar and
got it was a free seminar right what am
I doing in a free seminar I look to the
left I look to the right man if nobody
could motivate me and if I can't
motivate myself so I walked up out of
that seminar with nothing but fire with
nothing but glory and Blaze under my ass
I said I'mma build a company and I'm G
do it in nine months and that's where
the Comfort Killers came from
woo woo
so that's where it all came from let me
ask you so I like when the Comfort
Killers like The Branding you know
because like B created we do branding
and like what what gave you the
inspiration to create such a beautiful
brand like you know I go on your website
everything just looking nice and cream
like uh nice and clean and crisp you
know what I mean like yeah you know it
looks good I was I'm a nerd man so you
know I I I learn a lot I learned a lot
about Brandon By Doing Brandon by
reading by failing um so I I worked on
that website myself that was the one of
the first things I did when I walked out
of the seminar I was work on the website
but I wanted the color to punch people
in the face cuz I give no backpacks
right this is a loud brand I'm loud I'm
loud and I'm proud so The Branding came
as a result from how I was feeling we
got to be here and we got to be strong
so the Comfort Killers is negative right
doesn't it sound like negative ass words
that's right right the comfort is
negative to me and killer negative as
hell I looked on Google and it was
serial killers I was like man I got to I
got to be number one in Google cuz all I
see is serial killers so it is a
negative thing but two negatives in this
case does equal a positive Brandon just
came from the spirit at that point damn
damn yo damn you're not I I don't know
if it's a nerve but you're all about
your business and that's what I respect
about you like you guys this is what
happened folks Stacy AC cross and Shane
the train broke the fourth wall they
broke the fourth wall of the interwebs
and took the internet life and took the
hustle and made it
three-dimensional by adding a component
they took there from two different
places Shane being from York you know
and and and uh and Stacy from
Philadelphia and they they made a put a
third dimension and came together live
that was crazy and when you look inside
Stacy's
home she got Comfort Killers right on
the wall she's got diffusers she's got
lighting you know that's what I respect
about you Stacy because you're all about
your business you know you got to be
because you know what out there's not
sweet you know what I mean so like why
are why do you drive so hard what is it
that gives you that that that energy yo
here's the thing man they I paid with
energy because I didn't have the money
sir right so if you don't have the money
you got to look for other forms of
currency right so I looked I picked up
some attitude I got Infinity I got a I
got a whole lot of an abundance of
attitude I got a whole abundance of
efforts of discipline so and I got a
whole abundance of energy so I paid with
energy so here's the thing I used to
never invest in myself in my business I
would I would talk the talk but I didn't
walk the walk if I had five pennies to
my name God damn it at this point is
going back into business so that's why
when you come in here everything is the
Comfort Killers that's why I sped home
to do this show with you today cuz
everything is about business when I walk
the walk now it's because I had talk the
talk
baby you know what I mean everything got
to be about business Ryan man I messed
up a lot a lot of times in my life I
messed up I failed a bunch and I thank
all those failures I started companies
after companies from the age of 19 all
the way to 2930 so here's the deal I
know what it's like to fail and I
appreciate all those failures for
teaching me a valuable lesson baby and I
got closer to success after each one of
those
failures so oh I I think the audio cut
out there for a second so can you repeat
that last thing again I said I got
closer to success after each of those
failures baby that's right you know and
like you dig a lot of like I think in
life a lot of us dig holes and we feel
like we can't get out of these holes and
you know what sometimes we don't even
sometimes we may be walking to our
destination and we fall through the
cracks but ain't nobody ever realized
that you can dig yourself out of the
hole you could create steps elevated
steps to get to where you need to go you
know you don't have to make that big
leap because graphy doesn't allow us to
make that big leap we got to carve steps
in the hole so that we can get where we
need to be and that's the thing is that
every day you can grind a little bit
right we're building bricks of success
and then we look back and we see a big
house because every day we're taking
those small steps right and you know I'm
not happy where I'm at I'm going to
never I'm never going to be happy where
I'm at because you know what I'm a human
being and we're always going to be
rising you know what I respect about
what you said earlier I just want to
bring it back to the rapping is that you
said that people didn't want to hear you
rap you know and I I I I know a lot of
rappers I know a lot of people in the
community that never give up on their
dreams but they're not also listening to
the people what the people want and that
shows that you know a lot about business
a lot about marketing did you have any
like uh experience behind that like did
you go to school did you get a degree in
it like what what did you like where did
you get all of that Knowledge from
here's the thing I've been on the
internet since the internet was born
right I was on infos seek searching when
infos seek was here when geoc cities was
here I use knowledge and I look man I am
I pay attention to a lot of things so no
I didn't go to school I went to the
School of Hard Knocks I went to the
school of experience I went to the
school of failure I went to the school
of try try again I read a tons of books
on the subject if I'm interested I'm
going to learn it my friend so no and
here's the thing with with rapping
because I could keep pushing that door
down right we could keep pushing that
rapper door down but I wasn't living on
purpose so there's a lot of purposeful
rappers out here that's living on
purpose that's their thing but my thing
is to teach Millions how to get
uncomfortable to think better act better
and live better so I wasn't on purpose
so no matter how much I pound that wall
I was always going to be stopped and it
takes self-awareness it takes major
Consciousness and a shift a shift baby
to understand what your purpose is
that's right and and you know I I I left
school without a high school education
without a degree but you know it was
perseverance and it was all the people
that told me not that you could not
succeed you know that you could not make
it and and and and I just kept on
reading man I had dyslexia but that
didn't stopped me because you know what
wanting to prove those people wrong was
my motivation now I don't have to prove
anybody wrong you know what I mean only
person I got to prove is myself but who
were there people were there specific
people in your life that prevented you
where were made you believe that you you
probably would not be successful like
did you were there negative forces in
your like any specific
incidents yes so I got someone looking
before we go on could you make my screen
bigger please yeah for sure just one
second should I stop moving do do are
you on your phone or on a webcam I'm in
the I'm on the webcam on a webcam okay
just one second let me uh it's just the
way that this um this thing is so I'm
going to just zero because I move a lot
yeah no doubt no doubt yeah thanks yeah
this is uh work in progress we uh this
is uh we're this is in we're in beta
mode so can you move and I'll answer
that question can you move uh to the
yeah uh if you can move a little bit
yeah right a little bit sorry yeah
Center I'm like left right should I be
saying left or right just give me a few
seconds let me um yeah right there and
then we're gonna crop out yeah all right
all right give me a few seconds let me
Crop this out what's going on guys
that's what I love about this is that
we're doing this live we got shanea
train in the house we got David body we
got Cory Smith in the house like this is
amazing man this is awesome man I'm
telling you killing it with the hustle
on I love it yeah yeah and you're
killing it with the Comfort Killers like
you you're just bringing it and you're
bringing Al and then you're bringing
that Jamaican you know I could hear it
in your voice that's why I said pick up
your damn self man like from the islands
man the islands people don't understand
how the hustle is real in the islands
you I went to Jamaica a couple years ago
um and like just seeing
everybody grinding like it don't matter
who you are don't matter where you live
people on the street grinding if they
got a mango tree they go out there and
they get the grind and we're a lot of us
are so comfortable with our situation
and down there in in in uh back in ja
nobody's comfortable and it always Rises
to the top that's why I love you know
the Caribbean spit that's why you know
when people come from the car Caribbean
over here in Canada they succeed they
they they they they they they they kill
everybody they kill everybody in
performance work that's cuz they came to
work they didn't come to play they come
to
work okay I got your screen up yes yes
yes it's working all right I am Stacy AC
cross and there is no e in my name the
Comfort killers. comom baby yes so back
to the question so yeah who what like
cuz everyone has an experience what was
your experience where you had that one
person that said you can't do it or you
know or they try to prevent you from
achieving man you know what honestly man
I wish I wish I could tell you I have an
experience maybe maybe they're being too
silent and I don't know but here's the
deal I am in competition with myself so
I don't even hear anyone else I snip
snip C and chop off the fat Meat Man
here's here's the thing I don't even
hear nobody I can't see nobody um you
know I'm trying to de dive and try to go
back into a specific time there is none
I didn't hear anybody I'm sure people
are thinking that though don't get it
twisted I'm sure but I'm just not
focused on that that maybe I can't even
hear them I'm on the fifth they're
playing on the
third that's a good answer you know and
I always say that to people is like when
it comes to competition you know the
only thing is is that like I was saying
that earlier in the broadcast that you
know you should be like you have so many
good people if if you have competition
that's doing something better than you
right then just adopt it right because
you're going to you're going to move
like we're we're like even though we may
be directly in competition with each
other because we do the same things or
whatever but if you're doing something
really good I'm going to cop it I'm
going to do what it takes to elevate
because if I'm not looking at you and if
I'm not learning from you then I'm not
going nowhere you know what I mean so
it's all self-development and you can
never that's why we have to eat a humble
pie you never don't ever expect to to be
at the top in your head right you know
what I mean you people observe you being
at the top because you are at the top
like you're Stacy a cross yo here's the
thing man I I try to be at the top of my
game like I I make the I make my own
rules right and um I play by my own
games so that's why I said it's
unrealistic that I made it to Miami
sitting in front of grand Cardone
breathe in the same air it's unrealistic
to people because they can't understand
in such a short amount of time but they
don't see the late nights and the early
mornings right they don't see that book
red they don't see the failure they
don't see the trials they don't see me
up at night building that strategic War
plan that battle plan hitting my targets
they don't see the they don't see that
baby so when they do see me in front of
grand Cardone they think the shit's
sweet shit's not sweet I come back and
I'm way past it they want me to talk
about last week I'm not g talk about
last week let's talk about 2017 bab
that's right that's right so let let me
let me ask you now um if you can look
back and uh and this will be the the
final question but if you could look
back and um look at your old self the
young
self what would you tell her woohoo I've
been waiting for this question thank you
so much for being the first one to ask
me it hey man St hey Stacy Stacy Stacy
you need to calm down right uh you have
such a high purpose but here's the deal
I'm not trying to tell you the pathway
to take cuz I want you to do the same
exact thing because we're going to get
to this place together see I don't want
to change anything about my past baby I
appreciate my past so I'm going to let
my old self go through it again because
I know that my old SM my old self is
intelligent enough to get to the point
where I am now to get that aha moment
yeah I don't want to change history baby
I'm trying to make my future so there's
nothing that I will tell my old self
other than keep doing what you're doing
keep failing keep growing keep doing it
baby cuz you going to get there and then
put them
back will be born so there's nothing I
would tell my old self other than keep
moving and keep grooving baby oh
beautiful answer you got the right
things to say it's like candy in my ear
ear candy I I want to ask you one more
thing I got a favor to ask can you can
you spit something for all of us you
know ms's gotta call each other out I
knew gonna do it I knew you were gonna
do it yeah I knew all right so all right
so here's the thing you could get my I
got over 200 songs man no one knows
about them but here it
is Step the F back and stop creeping on
me I spit at 79 M articulate artillery
with me you couldn't feel me if I was
spitting or dazzle with the skills they
lacking they beting me it's never
happening you know just a little bit
just a little bit and that's that's not
a freestyle it's definitely a written
yeah but
still you know hey Ryan you hey that's
what we do
hey you got me all stunned I want to
hear more I want to hear you rap so Hey
listen yeah go ahead oh what were you
gonna say I was gonna say though if if
people are still interested in that I do
have some things online but we got to
search it man we got to search for it
strzy strizzy 88
well stzzy well let how do I um let
people know how how can we find you all
right so I'm everywhere because I'm
always there omnipresent you know you
got me on Facebook so please guys add me
on that just um just lead me there lead
me on Twitter at staca Cross I write a
bunch of Articles from the time of
February 1st February 14th when I walked
out the seminar I wrote over a 100
articles till now right so we're on
YouTube just type the come for killers
and we're not the serial killer type
we're the personal development making it
cool again type so I'm everywhere baby
Stacy a cross on everything and then how
do you spell your rap name so we can
find it because I'm I'm definitely G I'm
gonna find it strzy 88 strizzy okay so
how do you spell that I'm
likey strizzy 88 you know I'm not trying
to say it
man come on
man you going to be like damn you in a
whole different world man I was I was in
a whole different world so that's for
you right there yeah that oh well I I
appreciate it I appreciate you having
that much respect for me to to to to
come on this show to Grace the stage and
again folks and I'm going to let you uh
introduce yourself one more time because
I every time I hear it I keep on saying
it inside the house and I'm like telling
my friends my sister I'm like there's
this girl she has a Philly accent it's
like my name is Stacy cross and there is
no e in my
we got to do it one more time wait first
of all you said a Philly accent yeah I
don't know if it's a is it
a I'm conting I
apologize it's a New York
accent well you know I'm from Jersey
originally we moved from Jamaica Atlanta
in Jersey okay um so it's more like a
New York uh so I am
baby staca cross and there is no e in my
goddamn name yeah yeah yeah you guys can
pleas you visit her website Comfort
killers. comom um make sure you guys
check her out follow her and I hope that
uh we're gonna we do Jam sessions Lead
Me lead me not follow me Lead Me woo I
love it everything that she says is
positive everything that she says so
lead her you know find her lead her make
it happen you know that she got
merchandise and a beautiful merchandise
to to to sell buy it support it and you
got a do you have a book too I I wrote I
wrote a book I wrote an ebook within 24
hours it's called The Comfort killer
handbook I voiced it it's an audio book
and an ebook it's on my website I got
the 2017 War plan if you if you focused
on a successful 2017 it's the Comfort
killers. comom sl20 2017 War plan I
speak I want to speak at your local baby
showers I want to speak at your low
School proms I will do it your high
school
I'll speak anywhere man wow this is a
marketing Queen like she wrote a book in
24 hours don't tell me the hustle ain't
real this is the hustle this is the true
Spirit of the hustle Zone folks and yo
I'm going to remind you guys my name is
Ryan Perez AKA RPD God the wizard owner
of bowai creative for every website we
sell we donate free sites to
entrepreneurs with disabilities guys so
if you guys know people that have
disabilities that want to that don't
want to rely on the system please hit me
up message me go to my website W ww.bbc
creative withthe k.com and this is
the hustle Zone hustle Zone yo baby this
is the hustle Zone this is this is
worldwide we're hitting everywhere I'm
from Canada we're hitting Australia
we're H in United States we're talking
to people from Philadelphia from York
from Florida all kinds of places because
you know what hustle is universal so
make some noise for Stacy AC cross there
is no e in her name make sure you guys
hit up the Comfort Killers lead her lead
her we're all going to go see you guys
at the top this is the hustle Zone thank
you